ibotsolutions.com 2013-06-01

# IBOT Solutions - Privacy Policy

This website, composed and managed by The IBOT Solutions, contains information for people interested in Digital marketing, website development & Web Application. Entire content of the website has been gathered to the best of our knowledge and belief, and the company endeavors to keep it up to date. In particular, we reserve the entire right to update and/or modify and/or remove this data anytime and without any prior notice. Please note that the company holds no responsibility for incorrect or no longer correct statements, quotes or descriptions and thereby excludes liability for any losses resulting from such wrong information. 

Further, the company has every right to bring about legal action on people who misuse/alter/reproduce the content/ information available on the website. 

Data Privacy Policy

Our data privacy policy strictly conforms to the international legal regulations set down in accordance to the protection of data collected from people visiting our website. IBOT Solutions treats all personal data obtained via internet and our website carefully and confidentially so that no physical/mental harm is instilled up on the person, with regard to the collected data. Personal data that has possibly been known to us will be kept secret, privacy will be respected and information will be used exclusively for the purpose for which it was made known to us. Without seeking approval of the respective person, this data will neither be made accessible to third parties, nor transferred to them in any form or manner.

Rights over Intellectual Property

IBOT Solutions logos used on the website are protected by international Trademark laws. As such, they are strictly the property of IBOT Solutions and third parties are not allowed to use them until and unless getting an approval from the respective company.   
Pictures, Photos, Graphic Charts, Texts and Data published on the website may be used/ altered/ transferred/reproduced only with prior approval from IBOT Solutions.

Information Collected

Users of the website have an option to submit their name, contact information and their query to IBOT Solutions which is used to contact the requesting user with answers and more details in regards to the query submitted. 

Opt-Out Policy  

At any time, you may wish to remove / unsubscribe / delete your contacts / e-mail information from our side, all you need to do is to send an email at admin@ibotsolutions.com you will be notified with 48 hrs via e - mail prior to any actions taken as per your request. 

Changes to our Privacy Policy

IBOT Solutions reserves the entire right to modify/amend/remove this privacy statement anytime and without any reason. Nothing contained herein creates or is intended to create a contract/agreement between IBOT Solutions and any user visiting the IBOT Solutions website or providing identifying information of any kind.

Contact Details:

admin@ibotsolutions.com

**India Office:**  
Phone :+91 9539070845   
Email : admin@ibotsolutions.com

  * Our SEO campaign management system can track every aspect of your internet marketing campaign.
  * Dedicated research team that keeps track of the latest in internet marketing.
  * Provided **SEO solutions to the biggest** companies in the world.

"When we were developing our website, we were unaware about the importance of SEO. .."   
**Martin, Spice Holidays, Australia**  
Read More »
